(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ホロライブ0期生 7周年記念！
hololive 0th Generation 7th Anniversary!
公式メンバーシップ 限定壁紙・限定絵文字
Official Membership: Limited Wallpapers & Emojis
あれから7年たったよ。1人で立っていたステージも 今はたくさんの仲間でいっぱい！
7 years have passed since then. The stage I once stood on alone is now full of so many friends!
諦めずに歩いていてよかったね。 わたしは今幸せだよ。 SORA
I'm glad I didn't give up and kept walking. I'm happy now. SORA
ホロのぼー。もう美空にひとりぼっちじゃないよ！！
Holo-no-bo. You're not alone in the sky anymore!!
どんどんアップデートして色んな世界を見にいこうね♡ ろぼ子
Let's keep updating and go see many different worlds together♡ Roboco
デッカくなるぞ！！って意気込んで、たくさん頑張ったよね。
"I'll get big!!" With that spirit, you worked so hard.
今、本当にデッカくなれてるよ！！ 自分の思うまま突き進んでね☆ Suisei
Now, you've really become big!! Keep pushing forward as you see fit☆ Suisei
自信もないのに夢だけはずっとはなさなかったよね。
Even though you lacked confidence, you never let go of your dreams.
今たくさんの夢が咲いているよ！ 1人じゃない、みんなといっしょに。 さくらみこ
Now many dreams are blooming! You're not alone, we're all together. Sakura Miko
「ありえない」の向こう側へ！ 終わるはずだった世界から
Beyond the "impossible"! From a world that was supposed to end,
AZKiは今もまだこの世界でたくさんの仲間と一緒にいるよ！ 自分が決めた道を行け！ AZKi
AZKi is still in this world with many friends! Go down the path you've chosen! AZKi
行くよ！
Here we go!
Dream Story
ふと忘れてしまいたくなる
I feel like I might accidentally forget
昨日のあの記憶のピースね
Those pieces of yesterday's memories
失くしたりはできそうもないけど
It doesn't seem like I can lose them
うまく繋げばまた続きへ
But if I connect them well, they'll lead to what's next
でも今は関係ないんだよ
But that doesn't matter right now
そんなことも忘れちゃおよな
Let's just forget about all that
不思議な世界にアクセル全開で
With the accelerator floored into a mysterious world
飛び込もうよ一緒に
Let's dive in together
でもでも急ぎっぱなしは禁物で
But but, rushing all the time is a no-no
急がば回ってるっていうくらいじゃ
Better safe than sorry, as they say
だからたまにはゆっくりひと休み
So let's take a slow break once in a while
したらそれじゃそよ風のリズムで
And then go with the rhythm of the breeze
止まらねぇぞ！
We won't stop!
飛んでけハイ！大きく息を吸ったら
Fly away, high! Take a deep breath
僕らのストーリーが今溢れ出すよ
And our story starts overflowing now
もっともっと大きくね
Bigger and bigger
最初が肝心なんです！
The beginning is crucial!
はじめまして、こんにちは！せーの
Nice to meet you, hello! One, two...
ホロライブだよ！
It's Hololive!
もう一度ハイ！そら遠くまで届け
Once more, high! Reach out far into the sky
ドキドキまで奇想天外に彩っていく Dream☆Story
Unexpectedly, even to the heartbeat, painting our Dream☆Story
やっぱ一秒たりとも目を離さないで欲しいな
As expected, I don't want you to look away for even a second
まばたきもしてらんない
Can't even blink
ああ ほらね 最高でしょ？ イェイ！
Ah, see? It's the best, right? Yay!
一歩進めばまた後ろへ
Step forward, then back again
見えない力が邪魔している
An invisible force is getting in the way
ジャンプしたりできたらいいけれど
It'd be nice if I could jump over it
それも愛嬌　どうぞよろしく
But that's just part of the charm, so please bear with me
でも今は関係ないんだよ
But that doesn't matter right now
心響くリズムを辿れば
If we follow the rhythm that resonates in our hearts
不思議な世界の続きのページで
On the next page of this mysterious world
また出会えたね Destiny
We've met again, it's destiny
もしもし遅めのテンポもいいけど
Hello, a slow tempo is fine too
今はそんな場合じゃないわけじゃない？
But isn't right now not the time for that?
だけど大丈夫、一息ついたのならさ
But it's okay, if you've caught your breath
いちにのさんの合図で
On the count of three
いちにのさん！
One, two, three!
飛んでけハイ！大きな声で叫んだら
Fly away, high! If you shout out loud
僕らのストーリーが今紡がれてく
Our story will be woven together now
もっともっと大きくね
Bigger and bigger
ボリュームはMAXで！
With the volume at max!
はじめまして、こんにちは！せーの
Nice to meet you, hello! One, two...
ホロライブだよ！
It's Hololive!
もう一度ハイ！そら遠くまで響け
Once more, high! Resonate far into the sky
はちゃめちゃで摩訶不思議にきらめいたんだ Dream☆Story
Messily and mysteriously, it sparkled, our Dream☆Story
やっぱ一秒たりとも体感してたいの
As expected, I want to experience every single second
くらくらしちゃうくらい
So much it makes me dizzy
ああ だけど最高じゃない？
Ah, but isn't it the best?
ねえねえテンション 高まってアテンション
Hey, hey, tension, rising, attention!
ワクワク警報は鳴り止まない
The excitement alarm won't stop ringing
ねえねえテンション 高まってアテンション
Hey, hey, tension, rising, attention!
誰も止められないわ！
Nobody can stop us!
飛んでけハイ！大きく息を吸ったら
Fly away, high! Take a deep breath
僕らのストーリーが今溢れ出すよ
And our story starts overflowing now
もっともっと大きくね
Bigger and bigger
最初が肝心なんです！
The beginning is crucial!
これからもさ、よろしくね！せーの
From now on too, please treat us well! One, two...
ホロライブだよ！
It's Hololive!
最後はハイ！そら遠くまで届け
Last one, high! Reach out far into the sky
ドキドキまで奇想天外に彩ったんだ Dream☆Story
Unexpectedly, even to the heartbeat, we've painted our Dream☆Story
やっぱ一秒たりとも目を離さないで欲しいな
As expected, I don't want you to look away for even a second
まばたきもしてらんない
Can't even blink
ああ ほらね 最高でしょ？ イェイ！
Ah, see? It's the best, right? Yay!
みんなー、集合ー！
Everyone, gather 'round!
0期生ライブ、始まりましたー！
The 0th Gen Live has begun!
本日のハッシュタグはこちら！
Today's hashtag is this!
たくさんポストしてください！
Please post a lot!
そしてステージも見てー！
And look at the stage too!
ねー！
Hey!
はい！
Yes!
宝石をイメージしてステージを作ってもらいました！
They designed this stage with a jewelry theme in mind!
おおー！素敵ー！
Whoa! It's lovely!
ま、0期生初ライブなので
Well, since it's the first Gen 0 live...
気合入れてもらっちゃったよね、うちら。
...we really went all out with the production, didn't we?
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
そして、先ほど歌ったのがドリームストーリーだったんですけど
And we just sang "Dream Story" earlier...
はい。後ろに映像が流れてましたよね。
...and there was a video playing in the background, right?
流れてたー！
It was playing!
懐かしすぎた。
It was so nostalgic.
あちらですね、ファーストフェスの時の映像だったということで
That was actually footage from the First Fes...
4年半前でございます。
...which was four and a half years ago.
歴史を感じるね。やっぱ見ただけでわかるしね、なんかね。
You can really feel the history. You can tell just by looking at it.
なんか私たちの姿めっちゃ変わってない？
Don't we look totally different?
そうだよね、成長したんだよね。
That's right, we've really grown.
成長したよねー。
We sure have.
みこも成長したよね。
Miko has grown too.
成長したー！
You have!
あづきも。
AZKi too.
恥ずかしすぎたな。
That was so embarrassing.
エモいな。
It's so moving.
そんなね、私たちは今日はね、お互いのいろんな曲を歌っていくので
Anyway, we'll be singing various songs of each other's today...
どの曲を歌うか楽しみにしていてください！
...so please look forward to seeing which ones we perform!
はーい！
Okay!
では早速ですが、次の曲に行きましょう！
Now, without further ado, let's move on to the next song!
準備してきました！
We're ready!
お着替え行ってきまーす！
We're going to go change!
飛んで来な
Fly on over
めちゃ進む
Keep moving forward
都市部を抜けて遊び場へ
Through the city to the playground
いぇーい！
Yay!
ハジメノイッポ
作詞・作曲・編曲：ナユタン星人
Hajimeno Ippo
Lyrics, Composition, & Arrangement: Nayutalien
前人未到のトキメキ知りたい人？
Who wants to know an unprecedented thrill?
いっせーの いーんじゃない？
All together now, isn't it fine?
今だっていいんじゃない？
Isn't it fine right now?
希望の通り遊びたい人？
Who wants to play just as they hope?
それって君じゃない？
Isn't that you?
今日はいっちゃいいんじゃない？
Isn't it fine to go for it today?
タイム・イズ・マネー
Time is money
そりゃ何のマネ？
What kind of imitation is that?
寄り道こそ人生の醍醐味です
Detours are the best part of life
行きたい方にダッシュ
Dash in the direction you want to go
そんでハート奪取
And steal some hearts
この作戦 もう怪し隠すはない
This plan, there's no more hiding the suspicion
動かなかった足を
My feet that wouldn't move
今は踏み出したいと思える
Now I feel like I want to take a step forward
一人ではできなかったこと
Things I couldn't do alone
やっちゃうよ？行っちゃうよ？いっせーの！
I'll do it! I'm going! One, two!
一層一層さ ぶっ飛んでいくぞ
Higher and higher, we're gonna blast off
ぐんぐんこの調子 霧はまだまだ
Keep up this pace, the mist is still there
でも一歩一歩って 進んでいくぞ
But step by step, we'll keep moving forward
これが我らの第一歩
This is our first step
しかと見ていてくださいな
Please keep a close watch on us
転んだり迷ったり浮き足立たせ
Falling, getting lost, getting restless
もうちょっと付き合ってくださいませ
Please stick with me a little longer
跳躍時だてに 減速なんてございません
There's no slowing down when we're jumping
飛んで来な
Fly on over
めちゃ進む
Keep moving forward
都市部を抜けて遊び場へ
Through the city to the playground
いぇい！
Yay!
もしや今 とてもいい感じ？
Could it be that things feel great right now?
もっとギア上げちゃっていい感じ？
Is it okay to shift into a higher gear?
今日という日は
Today is the day...
だから目一杯 声出してみよう Let's go! Say!
...so let's shout at the top of our lungs! Let's go! Say!
(Wow Wow Wow) 世界一大きく
(Wow Wow Wow) The loudest in the world
(Wow Wow Wow) いいよもっともう一回
(Wow Wow Wow) Nice, one more time
(Wow Wow Wow) 宇宙一楽しく
(Wow Wow Wow) The most fun in the universe
うん、めっちゃ最高！
Yeah, it's absolutely awesome!
少しもやっていた未来
A future that was a bit hazy
今は期待とかしてみちゃう
Now I find myself looking forward to it
君がいたから見れた景色
The scenery I could see because you were there
やっちゃうよ？行っちゃうよ？いっせーの！
I'll do it! I'm going! One, two!
一層一層って 突っ込んだものの
I charged in further and further, but...
どんどん待ってるでっかい世界にクラクラ
...the vast world waiting for me makes me dizzy
でも一歩一歩を 大事にするぞ
But I'll treasure every single step
それが我らの第一歩
That is our first step
一層一層さ ぶっ飛んでいくぞ
Higher and higher, we're gonna blast off
ぐんぐんこの調子 霧はもうすぐ
Keep up this pace, the mist will clear soon
この一歩一歩を 楽しんでいくぞ
I'm going to enjoy every single step
それじゃみんなで第一歩
Now then, everyone together for the first step
しかと見ていてくださいな
Please keep a close watch on us
転んだり迷ったり浮き足立たせ
Falling, getting lost, getting restless
もうちょっと付き合ってくださいませ
Please stick with me a little longer
跳躍時だてに 減速なんてございません
There's no slowing down when we're jumping
ずっと見ていてくださいな
Please keep watching us forever
そっぽ向いてる未来はいりません
I don't need a future that looks away
両目をごらんくださいませ
Please look with both eyes
跳躍時の鼓動に退屈なんてございません
There's no boredom in the heartbeat when jumping
飛んで来な
Fly on over
めちゃ進む
Keep moving forward
都市部を抜けて遊び場へ
Through the city to the playground
いぇい！
Yay!
ダメダメ ダメダメ
No way, no way
シュガーラッシュ
作詞・作曲：DECO*27
編曲：TAKU INOUE
Sugar Rush
Lyrics & Composition: DECO*27
Arrangement: TAKU INOUE
やっぱパパッパッパ
As expected, pa-pa-pa-pa
やっぱりポッポッポッにしたい
I still want to make it pop-pop-pop!
やわなポッポッ諸症状で
With soft pop-pop symptoms,
私世界バッテ・オーライがって
I'm getting all right with the world's battery.
ノンノンなんてなってんだ
What's with all the "non-non"?
湿っぽいポイでさ歌っちゃって
Throwing away the dampness and singing along.
どうにかなることと
Things that'll work out,
ならないことね　わくわく
and things that won't. So exciting!
さくらってモラみこの時代よ
This is the era of Sakura and Mora-Miko!
知りたい　嘘つきたい　勝ちたいよ　日向
I want to know, I want to lie, I want to win, Sunbeam!
未体験じゃんけんだ　オイ　オイ
It's an unexperienced rock-paper-scissors. Oi! Oi!
ヤバイ　Sugar Rush　アゲチュンチュンにさせて
Oh no! Sugar Rush, make me feel all hyped up!
もっと　もっと　おたべ　召しませ
Have some more, more, please eat up!
変幻自在のドキドキが
This ever-changing heart-pounding feeling,
Because ぱんぱかぱんぱぱらっぱんでもう一回
Because pan-paka-pan-paparappan, one more time!
Sugar Rush　アゲチュンチュンばやしして
Sugar Rush, give me that hyped-up rhythm!
もっと　もっと　踊る　求めて
More and more, seeking to dance!
全然足んないよ　そんな数じゃ
It's not enough at all, with just that amount!
Because ぱんぱかぱんぱぱらっぱんでもう一回
Because pan-paka-pan-paparappan, one more time!
教えて Sugar Beat 触れないと
Tell me, Sugar Beat, if I don't touch it...
やっぱポッポッポッにしたい
I still want to make it pop-pop-pop!
遊びたい騒ぎたい全部忘れたい泣きたい気持ち　しくしくしくしく
I want to play, party, forget everything, a feeling like crying, sob-sob-sob!
頭と体バラバラ　まだまだ行けるわ長距離
Head and body all apart, I can still go the distance!
強がり快感　パニックになっちゃえば
Feeling good being tough, just getting into a panic!
最初はグッとやる気満々
At first, I'm all full of motivation!
だけどちょっと辛いからダンダン
But it's a bit tough, so bit by bit...
マイクとパッと切り替えて
Quickly switching with the mic!
本気負けで愛顧それも怖キャラ
Losing for real and getting favors, that's a scary character too!
最初はグッとやる気満々
At first, I'm all full of motivation!
だけどちょっと辛いからダンダン
But it's a bit tough, so bit by bit...
マイクとパッと切り替えなきゃ
I've gotta switch quickly with the mic!
ダメダメダメダメ
No, no, no, no!
とんでもないことは　望んでいるのだ　わくわく
I'm wishing for something unbelievable. So exciting!
しながら死にたくて　笑いたい
I want to die while doing it, and I want to laugh!
叶えたい　上がっちゃうの止めないで
I want to make it come true, don't stop me from rising!
安い世界なんて　ポイ　ポイ
Toss away this cheap world!
ださい情緒まちまえ　エイ　エイ
Mix up those tacky emotions. Hey! Hey!
ヤバイ　Sugar Rush　アゲチュンチュンにさせて
Oh no! Sugar Rush, make me feel all hyped up!
もっと　もっと　おたべ　召しませ
Have some more, more, please eat up!
変幻自在のドキドキが
This ever-changing heart-pounding feeling,
Because ぱんぱかぱんぱぱらっぱんでもう一回
Because pan-paka-pan-paparappan, one more time!
Sugar Rush　アゲチュンチュンばやしして
Sugar Rush, give me that hyped-up rhythm!
もっと　もっと　踊る　求めて
More and more, seeking to dance!
全然足んないよ　そんな数じゃ
It's not enough at all, with just that amount!
Because ぱんぱかぱんぱぱらっぱんでもう一回
Because pan-paka-pan-paparappan, one more time!
教えて Sugar Beat 触れないと
Tell me, Sugar Beat, if I don't touch it...
化けて出ちゃうよ　死なないよ
I'll come out as a ghost! I won't die!
Because ぱんぱかぱんぱぱらっぱん
Because pan-paka-pan-paparappan...
ダメダメダメダメ
No, no, no, no!
ノーダメダメダメダメ　Oh yeah
No, no, no, no, no! Oh yeah!
サクラカゼ
Sakura Kaze
作詞・作曲・編曲：ハム
Lyrics, Composition, & Arrangement: Hamu
窓に当たる陽を横目で眺めて　そっと陰る木の根に一人で比べてた
Gazing sideways at the sun hitting the window,
I quietly compared myself to the shadows of the tree roots.
積もる溜息を吹き払うように　そんな私を君が見つけてくれたんだ
As if blowing away my accumulating sighs,
you were the one who found me like that.
そう　それは恋のような温もりを全部　君に笑顔咲かせたら
Yes, if I could make all that warmth, like love,
bloom into a smile for you...
サクラカゼに踊る空　君と出会ったこの場所で
The sky dances in the cherry blossom breeze,
in this place where I met you.
どれくらいの想い出ぎゅっと　溢れそうになるかな
How many memories will I hold tight
until they're about to overflow?
君と流した涙は　明日の笑顔の糧にしよう
The tears I shed with you,
let's make them nourishment for tomorrow's smiles.
膝をついてたってほら　何度だっていいよ
Look, even if you fall to your knees,
it's okay, however many times it takes.
意地を張って恥をかいて　いじけたってそれでも
Being stubborn, being embarrassed, even sulking, despite it all...
君が傍で見守ってくれたこと
The fact that you watched over me by my side...
分かってるから
I understand that now.
追い風を受けて止まらない日々も　そっと挫けそうになって心が渦巻いた
Even on days when I couldn't stop, pushed by the tailwind,
my heart would swirl, on the verge of giving up.
積もる溜息でまた泣きかけても　温かな手でずっと支えてくれたんだ
Even when I was about to cry again from accumulating sighs,
you were always there to support me with your warm hands.
ほら 耳を澄ませば
See, if you listen closely
一人じゃないから
Because you're not alone
諦めかけて心が閉じても
Even if you're about to give up and your heart closes
君が背中を押してくれたよね
You pushed me forward, didn't you?
春の蕾が花開く頃は
When the spring buds begin to bloom
隣で笑い合おうね
Let's laugh together side by side
桜風に踊る空 君と出会ったこの場所で
The sky dancing in the cherry blossom breeze, here where I met you
どれくらいの思い出 ぎゅっと溢れそうになるかな
How many memories will overflow as I hold them tight?
君と描く言の葉は 未来もきっと残るから
The words I draw with you will surely remain in the future
汗をかいた後は そうさ 強くなれるんだ
After sweating it out, yes, we can become stronger
意地を張って 恥をかいて いじけたって それでも
Being stubborn, being embarrassed, even if we sulk
君がそばで見守ってくれたから
Because you were there by my side watching over me
ありがとうだよ
Thank you so much
君と出会えたこの空 これからもずっと咲かせるよ
This sky where I could meet you, I'll keep it blooming forever
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us now
この心に君のカケラがいるから
Because there's a piece of you in this heart
一人じゃないから
Because I'm not alone
Capture the Moment
作詞 金丸佳史 / 中野領太 作曲・編曲 中野領太
Lyrics: Yoshifumi Kanamaru / Ryota Nakano Composition & Arrangement: Ryota Nakano
いつか描いた文字の中
In the letters I once wrote
目を閉じた先に色付く景色が揺れた
A colorful landscape swayed before my closed eyes
少し戸惑う風の中
In a slightly confusing wind
重なる花びら 私たちの声
Overlapping petals, our voices
一瞬一瞬捕まえるみたいに
Like catching moment after moment
もっともっと踏み出せたら
If we could take even more steps forward
(We are one)
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us now
この心に君のカケラがいるから
Because there's a piece of you in this heart
強くなくてもいい
It's okay not to be strong
今の光を
This light now
僕と君と集う空に放つ
Unleash it into the sky where you and I gather
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせるから
Because we will gently make this miracle shine
力が湧くから
Because power wells up within
新たな種を握りしめ
Gripping a new seed
遠い未来へと強く願い込め蒔いた
I sowed it with a strong wish for the distant future
希望の風を吹かせては
Letting the wind of hope blow
理想の花びら 祈る明日の空
Ideal petals, praying to tomorrow's sky
何百億も光る星みたいに
Like tens of billions of shining stars
ずっとずっと終わらないから
Because it will never, ever end
この笑顔が過去を強く抱きしめて
This smile strongly embraces the past
今未来にこの手伸ばしてゆくから
Because I'm reaching out to the future now
時に転んでも
Even if we stumble sometimes
空を見上げよう
Let's look up at the sky
笑い日々を刻んでゆく
Carving out days of laughter
次の夢を掴み取るって約束するから
Because I promise to grasp the next dream
踏み出そうここから
Let's step forward from here
(We are with you We are with you)
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to keep looking at the same future
あの夢手にしてたい
I want to keep holding that dream
(We are with you Capture The Moment)
触れた奇跡の中で
Within the miracle we touched
その先まで続く空にまぎれたら
If we get lost in the sky that stretches beyond
君の場所と今を繋げたくて
Wanting to connect your place and the present
あの涙が今の僕らをつなげて
Those tears connect us now
この心に君のカケラがいるから
Because a piece of you is in this heart
強くなくてもいい
It's okay not to be strong
今の光を
The light of now
僕と君と集う全ての空に放つ
Releasing into the entire sky where you and I gather
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせるから
Because we will gently make this miracle shine
咲かせようここから
Let's make it bloom from here
一人じゃないから
Because you are not alone
(We are one)
褪せたハチミドリ
Faded Honeybird
作詞・作曲・編曲：宮田'レフィ'リョウ
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Miyata 'Lefty' Ryo
恋に恋してるあの子が
That girl who's in love with love
口ずさんでた流行りの歌
Was humming a popular song
反吐が出るくらい 甘い 甘い 言葉を踊って
Dancing to words so sweet they make me sick
くるまれてケミカルな菓子みたい
Wrapped up like a chemical candy
Ah Ah もういいよ
Ah ah, enough already
並べたセリフで飾って
Decorated with lined-up lines
隙あらば夜伽に誘って
Inviting to a night-watch at every chance
求愛行動ってやつさ 痴れ者暴れ獣
It's just a mating ritual, a foolish rampaging beast
気づいて 所詮愛なんて
Notice that, after all, love is just...
...建前どこにもありはしない
...a facade, it doesn't exist anywhere
信じたいけど
I want to believe, but...
どうせ叶わぬ約束 綻ぶ愛情
Promises that won't come true anyway, unraveling affection
ただ綺麗な言葉はいらない
I just don't need pretty words
未来永劫訪れない世界なら
If it's a world that will never come for all eternity
その手でいっそ止めて
Then just stop it with those hands
枯れた思い出に浮かぶハチミドリ
A honeybird floating in withered memories
二人肩並べ歩いた目黒通りの桜
The cherry blossoms of Meguro Street where we walked side-by-side
いつまでもずっとこのままでいようね
Let's stay like this forever...
...囁いた声のまやかし
...was the deception of a whispered voice
もういいよ 不埒な街を彷徨って
Enough already, wandering through this insolent city
着飾った安酒に酔って
Getting drunk on dressed-up cheap liquor
身を委ねておこう 私だって寂しいんだもの
I'll just surrender myself, because I'm lonely too
不敵な罪を重ねても
Even if I pile up bold sins
貴方は振り返りもしない
You won't even look back
分かってるけど
I know, but...
どうせ果たせぬ結実 綻ぶ愛情
Fruition that won't be achieved anyway, unraveling affection
あんなに好きを重ねていたって
Even though we piled up so much "love"
今じゃもう何事もなかったかのように
Now, as if nothing had ever happened...
...外れてしまうなんて
...it just comes apart
さよなら 純情 もう戻れないや
Goodbye, pure heart, I can't go back anymore
そんだけ大きな恋をしたんだ
I was in love that much
全てが空ろの嘘に見えても
Even if everything looks like a hollow lie
愛を探していく
I'll keep searching for love
どうせ叶わぬ約束 綻ぶ愛情
Promises that won't come true anyway, unraveling affection
ただ綺麗な言葉はいらない
I just don't need pretty words
未来永劫訪れない世界なら
If it's a world that will never come for all eternity
その手でいっそ止めて
Then just stop it with those hands
アザミナ
Azamina
ひらり ふらり 彷徨ってく 白い夢は もうやめた
Fluttering and swaying, wandering along, I’m done with that white dream.
私ずっと知ってたの 匂いに誘われて落ちてく
I’ve known it all along, lured by the scent and falling.
与えられた役目を尋ねることが怖くて
Afraid to ask about the role I was given.
流れる日々の答えに濁したのは心だけ
In the answers of passing days, only my heart was clouded.
定められた箱の中 味気ない寂しさが
Inside the predestined box, a tasteless loneliness.
少しずつ侵食してた 漂う地も知らぬまま
It was eroding me little by little, without me even knowing where I was drifting.
しまい隠したはずだった ただの戯言
It was supposed to be tucked away, just mere nonsense.
分かってる 奥に潜む その目で見たまぎれもない衝動
I know, lurking deep inside, is that unmistakable impulse you saw with those eyes.
ひらり ゆらりとんでいける 迷い惑い 閉じ込めた
Fluttering and swaying, I can fly away, trapping my hesitation and confusion.
あなたはもう 離さないで やがて嘘と知っても
Don’t let go of me anymore, even if you eventually find out it was a lie.
ひらり ふらり 彷徨ってく 白い夢は もうやめた
Fluttering and swaying, wandering along, I’m done with that white dream.
私ずっと知ってたの 匂いに誘われて落ちてく
I’ve known it all along, lured by the scent and falling.
まとわりつく言葉だけ 何の意味もないくせに
Only the words that cling to me, even though they have no meaning.
背負わされてる重さに 潰れそうでもがいてた
Struggling as I’m about to be crushed by the weight I’m forced to carry.
気付かないふりしていたの 交わすすべてを
I was pretending not to notice everything we exchanged.
囁いた我に染まる 覚悟と甘さの代償 それだけ
That’s all—the price of the determination and sweetness that stains the self I whispered.
ひらり ゆらり舞い降りてく 迷い惑い 脱ぎ捨てて
Fluttering and swaying, I dance down, casting off my hesitation and confusion.
あなたはもう 離さないで やがて嘘と知っても
Don’t let go of me anymore, even if you eventually find out it was a lie.
ひらり ふらり落とされてく 白い夢は もうやめた
Fluttering and swaying, being dropped down, I’m done with that white dream.
私きっと戻らない 匂いに誘われて落ちてく
I surely won’t go back, lured by the scent and falling.
ひらり ゆらりとんでいける 迷い惑い 閉じ込めた
Fluttering and swaying, I can fly away, trapping my hesitation and confusion.
あなたはもう 離さないで やがて嘘と知っても
Don’t let go of me anymore, even if you eventually find out it was a lie.
ひらり ふらり 彷徨ってく
Fluttering and swaying, wandering along.
白い夢は もうやめた
I’m done with that white dream.
私ずっと知ってたの 匂いに誘われて落ちてく
I’ve known it all along, lured by the scent and falling.
いのち(2024 ver.)
Inochi (2024 ver.)
息をしている だから生きている
I am breathing, therefore I am alive.
何度もずっと言葉を尽くしてきたんだ
I have used all my words over and over again.
息をしているように見えている
It seems as though I am breathing.
綻び出す私にとっての何か
Something that begins to fray within me.
鼓動がドクドクしている
My heart is thumping.
ここはいつも変わらずに
This place remains unchanged, as always.
急かし続ける音一つの命
A single life, a sound that keeps on rushing.
最後まで私のこと
Until the very end, about me...
...見届けてくれるの
...will you watch over me?
消えてしまいそうなの
I feel like I'm about to disappear.
わかってよ わかってよ ねえ
Please understand, please understand.
ホントのことなの
It's the truth.
いずれは卒業するんでしょう
Someday I'll graduate, right?
日常に戻ったら
When I return to daily life,
私は いなくなるの
I will be gone.
命のような 夢を見てるよ
I'm having a dream like a life.
またね バイバイ
See you later, bye-bye.
息をしている
I'm breathing.
だから生きている
That's why I'm alive.
見ためと中身の境界線 跨いで戻って
Crossing the boundary between appearance and essence and returning.
音が止まって
The sound stops,
動かなくなって
and stops moving.
そんな私を君は笑ってくれるかな
Will you smile at me like that?
鼓動がトクトクしている
My heart is beating fast.
ここはいつも変わらずに 巡り続ける
This place keeps on turning, unchanging as ever.
キボウしたいの 命
I want to hope, my life.
最後まで私のこと 見届けてくれるの
Will you watch over me until the end?
縋ってしまいそうなの
I feel like I might cling to you.
わかってよ わかってよ ねえ
Please understand, please understand.
真実を繋いだら もう二度と戻せないのに
Once the truth is connected, it can never be undone.
君が忘れちゃったら 私は いなくなるの
If you forget, I will be gone.
命のような 夢を見てるよ
I'm having a dream like a life.
またね バイバイ
See you later, bye-bye.
生き急いだあの日を 軽く弄らないで
Don't lightly mock those days when I lived so fast.
励まして
Encourage me.
それが生きる糧になるから
Because that will become the fuel for living.
大丈夫 ずっと私は 歌い続けるから
It's okay, because I will keep on singing forever.
最後まで私も 生きているか分からないけど
I don't know if I'll be alive until the end, either,
君がくれた言葉は 確かに残ってる
but the words you gave me certainly remain.
最後まで私のこと 覚えていなくてもいいから
It's okay if you don't remember me until the end.
いつ死んでしまうだろ 分かんない 分かんないよ
I don't know when I might die, I don't know, I don't know.
でも今君が笑えたこと それだけで意味があること
But the fact that you could smile now, that alone has meaning.
君が忘れちゃっても 私は 死なないから
Even if you forget, I won't die.
命のような 夢を見てるよ
I'm having a dream like a life.
またね バイバイ
See you later, bye-bye.
ここに宣言します
I hereby declare.
セブンスホイッスル
Seventh Whistle.
ラッキーセブンホイッスル
Lucky Seven Whistle
ひとつ やめるときも
One, in sickness and in health,
すこやかなるときも ずっと
and always in good health.
愛を 歌い続けることを
To keep singing of love,
堂々と誓います
I solemnly swear.
ふたつ 歌だとか ダンスももっと追求します
Two, I will pursue singing and dancing even more.
みっつ ずっと推してもらえる
Three, to be an idol
アイドルになってみせます
that you can keep supporting.
よっつめ 不安な
Four, even when anxious...
…未来も 私が照らすんだ
...I will light up the future too.
それでも 落ち込んじゃう日は
Even so, on days when I'm feeling down,
思い出しているよ みんなのその笑顔 その声を
I remember everyone's smiles and voices.
Happy Lucky Seven 革命
Happy Lucky Seven Revolution
Sunday Monday この先ずっと
Sunday Monday, from now on and forever
一緒だよね 約束
We'll be together, right? It's a promise.
ほらね笑う 門にそら来たる
See, Sora comes to those who smile.
Happy Birthday 毎日がほら
Happy Birthday, see, every day is...
Tuesday Wednesday Lucky Day
生まれ変わっても 迷わずに
Even if I'm reborn, without hesitation,
君だけの アイドルになるよ
I'll become your one and only idol.
何度も見つけてね
Find me again and again,
セブンスホイッスル
Seventh Whistle.
いつ アイドルとは
When they say an idol
時にあざとくが お決まりと
must be "azatoi" as a rule...
誰かが言ってたけど
someone said that, but
上手く 出来ないのです
I can't do it very well.
ねぇ もっと詰めて
Hey, get closer,
私から お願い 聞いて
listen to my request.
相思相愛 既読スルーなんてしないでよ
Mutual love, don't just read and ignore me,
私を見て
look at me.
Happy Lucky Seven 革命
Happy Lucky Seven Revolution
Sunday Monday この先ずっと
Sunday Monday, from now on and forever
一緒だよね 約束
We'll be together, right? It's a promise.
みんな笑う 門にそら来たる
Everyone smile, Sora comes to those who smile.
Happy Birthday 毎日がほら
Happy Birthday, see, every day is...
Tuesday Wednesday Every Day
7つ 全身全霊 かけて
With all seven, giving it my all,
ここにいる みんなのことを
for everyone who is here...
永遠に愛します セブンスホイッスル
I'll love you forever, Seventh Whistle.
そらちゃーん！ / いぇーい！
Sora-chan! / Yay!
新曲めっちゃ良かった！ / 良かったー！ / すごーい！
The new song was so good! / It was great! / Amazing!
初披露！ / 初披露！
First performance! / First performance!
おめでたいですね。 / おめでとー！
How wonderful. / Congratulations!
7周年おめでとう！ / ありがとうー！
Congratulations on your 7th anniversary! / Thank you!
でもちょっと複雑なんだけど、0期生全員の周年ではないんですよね。
It's a bit complicated, but it's not the anniversary for all of Gen 0.
そうなんだよね、みんなデビュー日が違ったりからね。
That's true, everyone has different debut dates.
それがね、こうやって集まったということで。はぁ〜…
But here we are, gathered like this. Phew...
セトリとかもめちゃくちゃ考えたじゃないですか。
We really thought a lot about the setlist, didn't we?
そうだね、組み合わせどうしようとか。
Yeah, like what combinations to do.
めちゃくちゃ悩んだ、大会議したよね。
We agonized over it, had a big meeting.
でもみこがすごいびっくりしたのは、0期生でこうやって集まっていろいろ考えると…
But what really surprised Miko was, when Gen 0 gathers like this and thinks about things...
もう誰かがメモを取って、誰かがまとめて、みたいな。
someone takes notes, someone summarizes...
すごく役割分担もしてたりとか。
We even had roles assigned.
みんななんか「任せるよ」っていうのがなく、こだわりがちゃんとあるから。
No one just says "I'll leave it to you," everyone has their own preferences.
すごい素敵だったなって。
I thought it was really wonderful.
チャンスだった、すごかったよ。 / 流石だったよ本当。 / 素敵だったよ。
It was our chance, it was great. / You were amazing, really. / It was lovely.
せっかくだから、スクショ撮りたい！
Since we're all here, I want to take a screenshot!
撮りたい！スクショ撮ろう！
I want to! Let's take a screenshot!
撮るぞ！ / どうやって撮る？
Let's do it! / How should we pose?
まずそらちゃんちょっと真ん中にいていただいて。
First, Sora-chan, please stay in the middle.
え、なんか上下とかになる？
Should we do like high and low positions?
え、待って、戦隊？ / どういう上下？
Wait, like Super Sentai? / What kind of high and low?
すぐにこういう時戦隊になるんだから。
We always turn into a Sentai team at times like this.
かん？ / はい、何のポーズ？
Ready? / Okay, what pose?
分かんない！何ですかこれ？
I don't know! What even is this?
いいじゃない！いいじゃない！
It's nice! It's nice!
周りにいない？パシャパシャ！いいじゃない！
Are there any others around? Click click! It's nice!
一番プリンセスみたい。えーと、他には？
She looks the most like a princess. Um, what else?
あ、客席側……あ、確かに。客席に行ってもらう。
Ah, the audience side... Ah, certainly. Let's have them go to the seats.
客席さーん！おいでー！
Audience members! Come here!
よくさ、座ってやるやつ撮りたい。
I want to take that photo where we sit down.
待って、これさ、この流れ知ってる。そらちゃんと客席と撮っていた時も毎回これ……
Wait, I know this flow. It was like this every time we took photos with the audience during Sora-chan's section too...
やったよ！同じことやったよ！自然とこうなっちゃうね。
We did it! We did the same thing! It just naturally ends up like this.
やっぱりやりたいじゃん！2024年も変わっていません！
We still want to do it! Nothing has changed in 2024!
エモだね。エモだね。エモだよねー！
It's emotional. It's emotional. It really is emotional!
あれもやるんじゃない？0期生列車。
Aren't we doing that too? The Gen 0 Train.
0期生列車！0期生列車！はい！いいよ、後で……
Gen 0 Train! Gen 0 Train! Yes! Okay, later...
行くよ！出発！0期生列車！
Here we go! Departure! Gen 0 Train!
待って、もしかして0期生天然多いのかな？やばいやばい、後で気付いた。
Wait, are there a lot of airheads in Gen 0? Oh no, I just realized.
楽しかった、楽しかった。進もう、次に。
That was fun, that was fun. Let's move on to the next one.
はい、というわけでね、楽しいMCもありましたが……
Yes, so, we had a fun MC section, but...
みんなさ、みんなのそらも見たいよね！
Everyone, you want to see everyone's Sora too, right!
見たいよねー！どうかな？
You want to see her, right! How about it?
ということで、ライブも中盤戦！まだまだ盛り上がっていくので、楽しんでください！
So, the live is in its middle stage! We're going to keep the excitement going, so please enjoy!
そらちゃん！
Sora-chan!
りるび
作詞・作曲・編曲：てにをは
Lilybe
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Tenioha
ねドクター ドクター めてしてよドクター
Hey Doctor, Doctor, fix me up Doctor
またいつもの例のバグ
Still that same old bug
ハッピー アラッキー 行き来するモード
Happy, Unlucky, going back and forth mode
組み立てゼンマイ式のココロどこだ
Where is my assembly wind-up heart?
おかしいね おかしいね くだらないね イヤイヤ
It's strange, it's strange, it's trivial, no no
わけないね わけないね ハイスペックなんて
It's easy, it's easy, something like high-spec
最先端の坊 やらわか滑走
Cutting-edge boy, soft gliding
ドキドキが止まりそう ネジ巻いて
My heart feels like it's going to stop, wind the spring
りるびなってゆくの覚えて ネジ巻いてネジ巻いてよ
Remember becoming Lilybe, wind the spring, wind the spring for me
ちょっとだけね ちょちょちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a little bit
ピッポッパポ鳴らして夢を作る
Beep boop, making dreams
ちょっとだけね ちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a little bit
でもちょっとだけじゃそのうち足りなくなるかも
But if it's just a little bit, soon it might not be enough
りるび りるび…… もっと
Lilybe, Lilybe... more
次は！ロボ子氏！
Next is! Roboco-shi!
マイネームイズエリート☆
作詞・作曲・編曲：キノシタ
My Name is Elite☆
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Kinoshita
ついに来たよお待たせ 待ちに待った うへへへ
I've finally arrived, sorry to keep you waiting! Wait for it, whe-he-he-he
電脳の世界からやって来た うざかわ系バーチャルにごアイドル
Came from the cyber world, an annoying-cute virtual idol
私はそうエリート なんていったってエリート
I am, indeed, elite! No matter what you say, I'm elite!
エリートみこ！エリートアイドル！そんなの常報に決まってるじゃん
Elite Miko! Elite Idol! That's obviously the basic information
意地悪も泣き虫も神様も 崇めたらみこパワーで
The mean ones, the crybabies, even the gods, if you worship me, with Miko Power...
幸せ分けてあげてもいいんだよ
I might just share some happiness with you
本物はエリートね！
The real thing is elite, right!
みこみこみこでホイホイうんにゃにゃ さくら、くら、くら、さくらみこ！
Miko miko miko, hoi hoi unnyanya! Sakura, kura, kura, Sakura Miko!
みこみこみこでホイホイうぐうぐ 明日から本気出す
Miko miko miko, hoi hoi uguugu! I'll get serious starting tomorrow
みこみこみこでホイホイうんにゃにゃ ぎゅっときわほにゃにゃにゃとも 幸せのぺこぽっこりみにみこ
Miko miko miko, hoi hoi unnyanya! Hug tightly... happy Pekopokkorimini Miko
みんな笑顔になーれ
Everyone, let's see those smiles
次は！みこち！
Next is! Mikochi!
画面の中の君が好き
作詞・作曲・編曲：瀬名航
I Like the You Inside the Screen
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Wataru Sena
君を初めて見つけた時
When I first found you
なぜか心揺さぶられたんだ
For some reason, my heart was shaken
すぐにものに命を宿す
Immediately breathing life into things
君の輝きは本物だった
Your radiance was the real thing
君は素敵だった
You were wonderful
画面の中の君が好き
I love the you inside the screen
その希少な君の顔が
That rare face of yours...
ただ君が笑えたらいい
I just want you to be able to laugh
本当の君とは実は違うとしても
Even if it's actually different from the real you
新しい扉を開けて息をしようよ
Let's open a new door and breathe
嘘も本当も関係ないから
Because lies and truth don't matter
息をしてる瞬間を僕らに届けていたいんだ
I want to deliver to us the moments you are breathing
君が好きだから
Because I love you
次は あずちゃん！
Next is, Azu-chan!
ソワレ
Soirée
見逃すな ソワレ
Don't miss it, Soirée
僕ら目撃者だ
We are witnesses
早急に手を伸ばした
I reached out quickly
水平線が誰か照らしたって
Even if the horizon shines on someone...
止めることなく君を繋ぐ架け橋渡ったら
If I cross the bridge that connects to you without stopping...
いつの日か ソワレ
One day, Soirée
君に届くまでさ
Until it reaches you
何度でも 呼び声を
Time and time again, the call
消えない軌跡 辿って
Following the indelible trajectory
幾星霜の果て どこまでも
To the end of countless years, everywhere
また抱いた ソワレ
I embraced it again, Soirée
今だ寝息を立て
Still breathing softly in sleep
太陽の瞳を盗んで
Stealing the sun's eyes
大胆さ さあ 逃げ出そうぜ
With boldness, come on, let's escape
朝まで響け 空を
Resonate until morning through the sky
跨ぐ栞を挟んだら
If I insert a bookmark that straddles...
約束だ ソワレ
It's a promise, Soirée
僕が眠るまでは
Until I fall asleep
何度でも また明日
Time and time again, see you tomorrow
拝啓 ソワレ
Dear Soirée
君へ読み継がれる僕たちの物語
Our story that will be read through to you
次は すいちゃん！
Next is, Sui-chan!
Step and Go!!
昨日から止まったような時計
A clock that seems to have stopped since yesterday
幼い頃をふっと思い出した
I suddenly remembered my childhood
もう心配しなくてもいいよ
You don't have to worry anymore
あの優しい声がそばにあったから
Because that kind voice was by my side
恋に傷ついて道にも迷った日もあったけれど
There were days when I was hurt by love and lost my way
いつだって探してたのは輝けるはずのBetter Day
What I was always looking for was a Better Day that should shine
Everyday 解き放て
Everyday, set it free
ためらわずそのエモーション
Without hesitation, that emotion
時代のせいにしたってつまらないよ
It's boring to blame the times
Everyday 君であれ
Everyday, be yourself
立ち止まる日もあるけれど
There are days when you stop in your tracks, but...
ねえきっと君は大丈夫
Hey, I'm sure you'll be fine
Step and Go!!
ray
作詞・作曲：藤原基央
Lyrics & Music: Motoo Fujiwara
お別れしたのはもっと前の事だったような
It feels like it's been even longer since we said goodbye
哀しい光は封じ込めて 踵すり減らしたんだ
I sealed away that sad light and wore down my heels
君といた時は見えた 今は見えなくなった
I could see it when I was with you, but now it's gone from my sight
透明な彗星をぼんやりと
I was vacantly watching a transparent comet
でもそれだけ探している
But that's the only thing I'm looking for
しょっちゅう唄を歌ったよ
I sang songs all the time
その時だけのメロディーを
Using the melody that existed only then
寂しくなんかなかったよ
I wasn't lonely at all
ちゃんと寂しくなれたから
Because I was able to properly feel lonely
いつまでどこまでなんて
How long, how far
正常か異常かなんて
Is it normal or abnormal?
考える暇も無い程
So much that I don't even have time to think about it
歩くのは大変だ
It's hard to keep walking
楽しい方がずっといいよ
It's much better to have fun
ごまかして笑っていくよ
I'll keep laughing and faking it
大丈夫だ あの痛みは
It's okay, that pain...
忘れたって消えやしない
won't disappear even if I forget it
理想で作った道を
The path I made with ideals
現実が塗り替えてゆくよ
Reality is painting over it
思い出はその軌跡の上で
Memories are on those tracks
輝きになって残っている
Remaining as a sparkle
お別れしたのは何で
Why did we say goodbye?
何のためだったんだろうな
I wonder what it was all for
哀しい光が僕の影を
The sad light casts my shadow...
前に長く伸ばしている
long and ahead of me
時々熱が出るよ
Sometimes I get a fever
時間がある時眠るよ
I sleep when I have time
夢だと解るその中で
Inside a dream I know is a dream
君と会ってからまた行こう
After I meet you, I'll go again
晴天とはほど遠い
It's far from a clear sky
終わらない暗闇にも
Even in the endless darkness
星を思い浮かべたなら
If I imagine the stars
すぐ銀河の中だ
I'm immediately inside the galaxy
あまり泣かなくなっても
Even if I don't cry as much
靴を新しくしても
Even if I get new shoes
大丈夫だ あの痛みは
It's okay, that pain...
忘れたって消えやしない
won't disappear even if I forget it
伝えたかった事が
The things I wanted to tell you...
きっとあったんだろうな
I'm sure there were some
恐らくありきたりなんだろうけど
They're probably commonplace
こんなにも
But even so...
お別れした事は
That we said goodbye
出会った事と繋がっている
Is connected to the fact that we met
あの透明な彗星は
That transparent comet...
透明だから無くならない
is transparent, so it never disappears
〇✕△どれかなんて
Circles, crosses, triangles, which one?
皆と比べてどうかだなんて
How does it compare to everyone else?
確かめる間も無い程
So much that there's no time to check
生きるのは最高だ
Being alive is the best
あまり泣かなくなっても
Even if I don't cry as much
ごまかして笑っていくよ
I'll keep laughing and faking it
大丈夫だ あの痛みは
It's okay, that pain...
忘れたって消えやしない
won't disappear even if I forget it
大丈夫だ この光の
It's okay, at the beginning...
始まりには
of this light...
君がいる
you are there
Ray of Jewelry
みんな、0期生ライブを見てくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for watching the Gen 0 Live!
早速ですが、告知のお時間です。
Without further ado, it's time for some announcements.
まずはこちら！
First up is this!
0期生ライブ記念グッズが出ます！
Gen 0 Live commemorative goods are coming out!
イェーイ！
Yay!
それでは、順番に紹介していくね。
Now, we'll introduce them one by one.
1つ目はこちら。
First is this one.
アクリルスタンド！
Acrylic Stands!
Tobi先生が書いてくれました。
Illustrated by Tobi-sensei.
みんなの分があるので、
Since there's one for everyone,
ぜひ全員分集めてください！
please collect the whole set!
次はこちら、
Next is this...
ロボ子紹介お願い！
Roboco, please introduce it!
はーい！
Okay!
こちらは、ガーランド風キーホルダー！
These are Garland-style Keyholders!
ガーランドをイメージした、アクリルチャームです。
They're acrylic charms designed like a garland.
それぞれをつなげて飾ることができるので、
You can connect and display them together,
0期生みんな、つなげてみてね。
so please try connecting all the Gen 0 members.
次は、みこっち！
Next up, Mikocchi!
はーい！
Okay!
次はネックストラップ付きチケットケースです。
Next is the ticket case with a neck strap.
イベントのチケットなどを入れられる、ネックストラップ付きのチケットケースです。
It's a ticket case with a neck strap for holding event tickets and such.
背景台紙付きで、ケースの中にアクリルスタンドを入れて、
It comes with a background card, so you can put your acrylic stand in the case
持ち運んでね。
and take it with you.
次は、すいちゃん！
Next, Sui-chan!
はい！
Yes!
次はランダム缶バッジ！
Next are the Random Can Badges!
華やかなデザインの缶バッジになっております。
These can badges feature a gorgeous design.
全10種のランダム仕様になっているので、ぜひたくさん集めてください。
There are 10 types in total, sold randomly, so please collect many of them.
次は、あずちゃん！
Next, AZ-chan!
はい！
Yes!
次はブランケット！
Next is the blanket!
今回の記念キービジュアルを大きく使用したブランケットになってます。
This blanket features the commemorative key visual in a large print.
冬のお供にいかがでしょうか。
How about it as a companion for winter?
ということで、そらちゃんにお戻しします。
And with that, I'll hand it back to Sora-chan.
はい！みんなありがとう。
Yes! Thank you everyone.
まだありますよ。
There's still more.
ブロマイドケース！
Bromide Cases!
0期生を応援してくれてるファンの皆様へ、
For all the fans who support Gen 0,
0期生全員からのメッセージ入りのブロマイドケースだよ。
this is a bromide case with messages from all Gen 0 members.
メッセージは届いてからのお楽しみ。
The messages are a surprise for when you receive them.
内容は複製になるので、お気をつけください。
Please note that the content is duplicated.
はい、というわけでグッズは以上になります。
So, that's all for the goods.
盛りだくさんだったね。
It was a lot, wasn't it?
今回は数量限定やセット販売はないので、
There are no limited quantities or set sales this time,
好きなものを単品でたくさんお買い求めください。
so please buy as many individual items as you'd like.
ここからはそれぞれ告知をさせていただきます。
From here, we'll each make our own announcements.
まずは私、ときのそらから。
First is me, Tokino Sora.
先ほどの私の7周年記念配信でも言いましたが、
As I mentioned in my 7th anniversary stream earlier,
ときのそら、7周年記念グッズもありますので、よろしくお願いします。
Tokino Sora 7th anniversary goods are also available, so please check them out.
そして、
And,
私ときのそらのニューシングル「おかえりなさい」が、
my new single 'Okaerinasai'
9月11日にリリースになります！
will be released on September 11th!
テレビアニメ「僕の妻は感情がない」オープニング主題歌として、現在オンエア中です。
It's currently airing as the opening theme for the TV anime 'My Wife Has No Emotion.'
そして、そして、そして、本日解禁になりました、
And, and, and, also revealed today,
「ラッキーセブンズホイッスル」もシングルに収録されます。
'Lucky Seven's Whistle' will also be included in the single.
こちらは7周年記念ソングとして制作しました。
This was created as a 7th anniversary song.
どちらもメモリアルな楽曲になっているので、いっぱい聴いてください。
Both are memorial songs, so please listen to them a lot.
次は、あずきちゃん！
Next, AZKi-chan!
はい、あずきです。
Yes, it's AZKi.
あずきからは、あずきメジャーデビューライブ「声色エントロピー」
From AZKi, the major debut live 'Kowairo Entropy'
追加公演、9月17日、18日、豊洲PITにて開催しますので、ぜひよろしくお願いします。
additional performances will be held at Toyosu PIT on Sept 17th and 18th.
え、そして現在、アルバム「Route If」が配信中、発売中です。
Also, the album 'Route If' is currently on sale and streaming.
ぜひこちらもよろしくお願いします。
Please check that out too.
次はみこっち！
Next, Mikocchi!
はい！
Yes!
みこからは、2024年10月26日土曜日に、
From Miko, on Saturday, October 26th, 2024,
さくらみこ 1stソロライブ「Flower Fantasista」開催決定です！
Sakura Miko's 1st Solo Live 'Flower Fantasista' is confirmed!
二次先行受付が、なんと明日23時59分までです。お忘れなきように。
Secondary advance lottery applications are open until 11:59 PM tomorrow. Don't forget.
そして、
And,
2024年9月25日に、1stアルバム「flower rhapsody」が発売決定しております。
on September 25th, 2024, the 1st album 'flower rhapsody' will be released.
各店舗にてまだまだ予約受付中ですよろしくね。
Pre-orders are still being accepted at various stores, so please check it out.
それでは、すいちゃん！
Now, Sui-chan!
はい！
Yes!
星街すいせいライブツアー2024「Spectra of Nova」の情報が解禁されました。
Information for Hoshimachi Suisei Live Tour 2024 'Spectra of Nova' is out.
さいたまスーパーアリーナ、舞洲アリーナ、サンパレスホテルホールで、
At Saitama Super Arena, Maishima Arena, and Sunpalace Hotel & Hall,
11月14日から12月28日でツアーが開催されます。
the tour will be held from November 14th to December 28th.
現地チケットの1次抽選も始まっているので、ぜひ皆さん応募してください。
Primary lottery for venue tickets has started, so please apply.
詳細はツアー特設サイトを見てね。
Check the tour website for details.
では、最後にロボ子！
Now, finally, Roboco!
はい！
Yes!
えっと、僕個人はないので、僕たちのチャンネル登録もぜひよろしくお願いします！
Um, I don't have personal news, so please subscribe to our channels!
そして、なんとですね、
And, amazingly,
0期生で現在9月5日から10月2日まで、
Gen 0 is having a collaboration from September 5th to October 2nd,
極楽湯コラボ開催中...
with RAKU SPA!
hololive × 極楽湯 RAKU SPA プロライブ
hololive x Gokurakuyu RAKU SPA Collab
開催中です！
It's now being held!
イェーイ！
Yay!
みんな僕たち0期生の湯に浸かりに来てください！
Everyone, please come and soak in our 0th generation's bath!
それでは、これからも0期生を...
Well then, please continue to...
よろしくねー！
...support the 0th generation!
hololive 0期生ユニット4周年記念配信
hololive 0th Gen Unit 4th Anniversary Stream